// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What type of speech context happens when two persons interact?",
    answer: "a. dyad",
    options: [
      "a. dyad",
      "b. mass communication",
      "c. public communication",
      "d. small group"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What type of speech context refers to communication that focuses on one person, in which the speaker acts as both the sender and receiver of the message?",
    answer: "b. intrapersonal",
    options: [
      "a. interpersonal",
      "b. intrapersonal",
      "c. mass communication",
      "d. public communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What type of speech context refers to the process of imparting information through television, radio, newspaper, magazines, books, billboards, internet and other types of media?",
    answer: "c. mass communication",
    options: [
      "a. interpersonal",
      "b. intrapersonal",
      "c. mass communication",
      "d. public communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of these types of speech context takes place and establishes a personal relationship between and among people?",
    answer: "a. interpersonal",
    options: [
      "a. interpersonal",
      "b. intrapersonal",
      "c. mass communication",
      "d. public communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which type of INTERPERSONAL context involves at least three but not more than twelve people engaging in face-to-face interaction?",
    answer: "c. small group communication",
    options: [
      "a. dyad communication",
      "b. sharing group communication",
      "c. small group communication",
      "d. team communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What type of speech context requires you to deliver or send the message before or in front of a group?",
    answer: "d. public communication",
    options: [
      "a. interpersonal",
      "b. intrapersonal",
      "c. mass communication",
      "d. public communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a speech context?",
    answer: "c. long story communication",
    options: [
      "a. dyad communication",
      "b. intrapersonal communication",
      "c. long story communication",
      "d. mass communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is/are involved in intrapersonal communication?",
    answer: "b. only one speaker",
    options: [
      "a. a small group",
      "b. only one speaker",
      "c. a speaker and an audience",
      "d. two speakers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following refers to the number of communicators and the setting in which the communication process takes place?",
    answer: "b. Speech context",
    options: [
      "a. Speech delivery",
      "b. Speech context",
      "c. Speech defect",
      "d. Speech communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "You spent the night reminiscing your happy moments with someone you are interested in and suddenly realized that you must prioritize your studies. What type of speech context is evident in the situation?",
    answer: "c. interpersonal communication",
    options: [
      "a. public communication",
      "b. mass communication",
      "c. interpersonal communication",
      "d. intrapersonal communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Speech Context refers to the number of communicators and the setting in which the communication process takes place.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: [
      "A.True",
      "B.False",
      "C.Halfway True",
      "D.Halfway False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "In dyad and small group communication, you have to listen carefully and understand what the other person is saying. Asking clarifying questions will let the other person know that you are indeed listening attentively.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: [
      "A.True",
      "B.False",
      "C.Halfway True",
      "D.Halfway False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Cheering yourself up before an important event and talking to yourself while completing a task are examples of interpersonal communication.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: [
      "A.True",
      "B.False",
      "C.Halfway True",
      "D.Halfway False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "To become a good communicator, you should at least know how to behave and respond to various speech contexts.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: [
      "A.True",
      "B.False",
      "C.Halfway True",
      "D.Halfway False"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Providing comfort to a friend who is feeling down, or simply talking with your classmates about your plans for a group activity is an example of dyad and small group communication.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: [
      "A.True",
      "B.False",
      "C.Halfway True",
      "D.Halfway False"
    ]
  },
];
